Guide to the Time Inc. Time-Life News Service Records 1935-1987 MS 3009-RG 14
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Chief of Correspondent Files, 1935-1987; 60.5 Linear feet in 60 record cartons, 1 flat box
  - Subseries I.D. General Files, 1944-1987; 46.95 Linear feet in 46 record cartons, 1 flat box
    - Powers, 1960 (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 12-13)
    - Prendergast, Curt, 1963-1979 (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 14-16)
    - Prendergast, Curt [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Press Release, 1976 (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 17)
    - Press Section, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 18)
    - Prince Saud: Lunch, 1979 (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 19)
    - Printing Requests, 1976 (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 20)
    - Project [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 21)
    - Project Mercury, 1961 (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 22)
    - Project Moscow Visit/Newstour, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 23)
    - Promotion, 1960 (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 24)
    - Publishing Reports, 1971 (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 25)
    - Punta del Este Conference, 1961 (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 26)
    - Queries, 1961-1966 (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 27)
    - Rabin, Yitzhak: Dinner: 1976 Jan., 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 28)
    - Rademaekers, Bill, 1958-1986 (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 29-31)
    - Rademaeker, Bill [RESTRICTED], 1968-1970, 1978-1985 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Raein, Parviz, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 3174, Folder 1)
    - Raein, Parviz [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Rauch, Rudolph Stuart, 1971-1983 (Offsite-box 3174, Folder 2)
    - Rauch, Rudolph Stewart [RESTRICTED], 1972, 1979-1981 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Reagan, Ronald, 1980 (Offsite-box 3174, Folder 3)
    - Refugee Relief Committee, 1975 (Offsite-box 3174, Folder 4)
    - Regional Ads, 1960-1962 (Offsite-box 3174, Folder 5)
    - Report of the European Task Force: An Opening in Europe, 1972 (Offsite-box 3174, Folder 6)
    - Republicans, 1960-1962 (Offsite-box 3174, Folder 7)
    - Research and Development, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 3174, Folder 8-9)
    - Researchers, 1975-1978 (Offsite-box 3174, Folder 10-12)
    - Rio, 1966-1983 (Offsite-box 3174, Folder 13-16)
    - Rio [RESTRICTED], 1964-1976 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Rio: Brazilian Foreign Press, 1966 (Offsite-box 3174, Folder 17-18)
    - Rio: Life, 1956-1960 (Offsite-box 3174, Folder 19)
    - Rio: Personnel, 1963-1972, 1983 (Offsite-box 3174, Folder 20-21)
    - Rio: Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Rio: Sports Illustrated, 1955-1958 (Offsite-box 3174, Folder 22)
    - Riyadh, Saudi Arabia, 1981 (Offsite-box 3174, Folder 23)
    - Robins, Eric, 1956-1978 (Offsite-box 3174, Folder 24-26)
    - Robins, Eric [RESTRICTED], 1964, 1975 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson, 1961-1976 (Offsite-box 3174, Folder 27)
    - Rogers, William P., 1973 (Offsite-box 3174, Folder 28)
    - Rome, 1974-1978 (Offsite-box 3174, Folder 29)
    - Rome [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Romney, George: Trip, 1965 (Offsite-box 3174, Folder 30)
    - Roots, John, 1972 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 1)
    - Roper, Burns, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 2-3)
    - Rosenthal, Abe: Latin America Program, 1982 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 4)
    - Rosholt, Mike: Barlow Rand Ltd, 1981-1983 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 5)
    - Rosholt, Mike: Barlow Road Ltd [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Rukeyser, William, 1981 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 6)
    - Rusk, Dean: 1962 Sept. 14 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 7)
    - Russia, 1961-1967 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 8-9)
    - S: Miscellaneous, 1969 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 10)
    - Sadat, Anwar: Egypt, 1972-1976 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 11)
    - Sadat, Anwat: Interview, 1972-1977 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 12-13)
    - Sadat, Anwar: Reception, 1975, undated (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 14-15)
    - Saddler, Jeanne, 1976-1978 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 16)
    - Saddler, Jeanne [RESTRICTED], 1977-1983 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Sahner, Marilyn, 1982 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 17)
    - Sales Meeting: South Carolina, 1978 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 18)
    - Salinger, J.D., 1961 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 19)
    - SALT II Symposium: 1979 May 1 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 20)
    - San Diego Flap: Gene Fuson, 1962 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 21)
    - San Francisco, 1962-1985 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 22-23)
    - San Francisco [RESTRICTED], 1971-1977 (Offsite-box R45)
    - San Francisco: Personnel, 1964-1971, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 24)
    - San Francisco: Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Sarawak Project, 1974 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 25)
    - Schefter, Jim, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 26)
    - Schindehette, Susan, 1977 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 27)
    - Schindehette, Susan [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Schlesinger, James: Lunch: Nov. 21, 1978 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 28)
    - Schoenburn, David, 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 29-30)
    - Schultz, Charles: Lunch, 1980 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 31)
    - Scott, Gavin, 1964-1972 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 32-33)
    - Scott, John, 1958-1985 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 34-35)
    - Scott, John [RESTRICTED], 1965, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Scott, John M.: Retirement, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 36)
    - Scott, John M.: Retirement [RESTRICTED], 1980-1981 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Selassie, Haile, 1963 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 37)
    - Seychelles, undated (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 38)
    - Shanahan, Jim, 1977 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 39)
    - Shields, Eileen, 1974-1981 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 40)
    - Shields, Eileen [RESTRICTED], 1977-1981 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Shulman, Marshall D., 1977 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 41)
    - Shultz, George: Breakfast, 1980-1986 (Offsite-box 3175, Folder 42)
    - Sider, Don, 1966-1980, 1986 (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 1-2)
    - Sider, Don [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Sidey, Hugh and Robert Ajemian: Party: 1978 May (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 3)
    - Sign [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 4)
    - Simpson, Jan, 1977, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 5-6)
    - Simpson, Jan [RESTRICTED], 1980-1983 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Siverd, Bonnie, 1977 (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 7)
    - Sjeklocha Affair, 1971 (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 8)
    - Skylab, 1973 (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 9)
    - Slug Memoranda, 1972 (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 10)
    - Smilgis, Martha, 1981 (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 11)
    - Smirkovsky, Josef, 1971 (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 12)
    - Smith, Rauch, and Cloud: Correspondence, Memoranda, and Research, 1977 (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 13-14)
    - Smith, William E., 1958-1963, 1969, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 15-18)
    - Soares, Mario: Lunch, 1978 (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 19)
    - Solzhebitsyn, 1974 (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 20)
    - South Africa, 1971 (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 21)
    - South Bronx: Tour: 1975 July (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 22)
    - Special Project [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 23)
    - Staff Memos, 1963-1978 (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 24-28)
    - Standards, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 29-30)
    - State Department, 1984 (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 31)
    - Steel Controversy, 1962 (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 32)
    - Steele, John, 1965-1977 (Offsite-box 3176, Folder 33)
    - Steele, John, 1963-1965 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 1)
    - Stevenson, Adlai, 1958-1960 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 2)
    - Stewart, Bill, 1978 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 3)
    - Striker, John, 1974-1979 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 4-5)
    - Stringers, 1972-1978 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 6-7)
    - Stringers [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Subpoenas, 1970-1974 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 8-9)
    - Suggestion: Query-Reply System Review, 1958 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 10)
    - Summer Employees, 1975 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 11)
    - Summer in the Cities, 1969 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 12)
    - Suro, Roberto, 1978-1985 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 13)
    - Suro, Roberto [RESTRICTED], 1979-1983 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Swan, Annalyn, 1963-1965 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 14)
    - Swinton, Stan, 1969-1972 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 15)
    - Sydney, 1960--1972 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 16-17)
    - Sydney: Personnel, 1962-1967 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 18)
    - Synanon [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 19)
    - Syndication, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 20)
    - Syndication [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box R45)
    - T,P and C Memoranda, 1975-1977 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 21)
    - Talbott, Strobe, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 22-23)
    - Taxes, 1967-1977 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 24-25)
    - Teamsters, 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 26)
    - Teheran, 1965, 1975-1979 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 27-29)
    - Television News, Inc., 1974 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 30)
    - Teletext, 1981 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 31)
    - Terry, Wallace: Coming Home Records, 1972 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 32)
    - Thatcher, Margaret, 1977 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 33)
    - Third World, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 34-35)
    - Thomas, Evan, 1977-1983 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 36-37)
    - Thomas, Evans [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Thomas, Larry: Bechtel Power Corporation, 1977-1983 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 38)
    - Time Canada, 1977-1983 (Offsite-box 3177, Folder 39)
    - Time Canada, 1975 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 1)
    - Time Edit, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 2)
    - Time Edit: Budget, 1975 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 3)
    - Time Employees Profit-Sharing Savings Plan, 1978 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 4)
    - Time Europe, 1974-1977 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 5-6)
    - Time Inc. History Projects, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 7)
    - Time International, 1976 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 8)
    - Time Lists, 1976-1978 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 9-10)
    - Time Nation, 1978 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 11)
    - Time Pacific, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 12-14)
    - Time Pacific: Meeting in Jakarta, 1973 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 15)
    - Time Picture Department, 1975 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 16)
    - Time Scene, 1978 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 17)
    - Time 60th Anniversary Gala: 1983 Oct, 1982 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 18)
    - Time-Life Books, 1975-1977 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 19)
    - Time-Life Films, 1977 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 20)
    - Time-Life Films: Alexander the Great, 1977 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 21)
    - Time-Life International: Budgets and Personnel, 1947-1956 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 22-23)
    - Time-Life News Service: America Revisited: Midwest Trip, 1965 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 24)
    - Time-Life News Service: Budget, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 25-26)
    - Time-Life News Service: Bureaus, 1968-1972 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 27-28)
    - Time-Life News Service: Bureaus: Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 29)
    - Time-Life News Service: Bureaus: Worldwide Cables and Memoranda, 1963-1969 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 30)
    - Time-Life News Service: Cost of Living, 1957, 1966-1970 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 31-32)
    - Time-Life News Service: Domestic and Foreign Bureau Rosters, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 33)
    - Time-Life News Service: Domestic and Foreign Bureau Rosters [RESTRICTED], 1968-1970 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Time-Life News Service: Operations, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 3178, Folder 34)
    - Time-Life News Service: Operations, 1964-1968 (Offsite-box 3179, Folder 1-2)
    - Time-Life News Service: Personnel, 1961-1969 (Offsite-box 3179, Folder 3-7)
    - Time-Life News Service: Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1961-1967 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Time-Life News Service: Stringer Reports: 1972 June 30 (Offsite-box 3179, Folder 8)
    - Tinnin, David, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3179, Folder 9-10)
    - Tinnin, David [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Tito, Josip Broz, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3179, Folder 11-12)
    - Tokyo, 1963-1984 (Offsite-box 3179, Folder 13-16)
    - Tokyo: Interns, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 3179, Folder 17)
    - Tokyo: Life, 1957-1965 (Offsite-box 3179, Folder 18)
    - Tokyo: Office Renovation, 1967 (Offsite-box 3179, Folder 19)
    - Tokyo: Personnel, 1957-1968 (Offsite-box 3179, Folder 20)
    - Tokyo: Sports Illustrated, 1964-1968 (Offsite-box 3179, Folder 21)
    - Tokyo: Time, 1955-1965 (Offsite-box 3179, Folder 22)
    - Traffic Desk, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 3179, Folder 23)
    - Training Programs, 1961-1964 (Offsite-box 3179, Folder 24)
    - Training Programs: Extra Letters: 1961, undated (Offsite-box 3179, Folder 25)
    - Training Programs: Extra Letters: 1961, undated (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 1)
    - Training Programs: Prospective Journalists: 1961, 1961-1963, 1969 (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 2-4)
    - Training Programs: Prospective Journalists [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Trip to Europe: 1986 Feb. (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 5-6)
    - Trudeau, Pierre Elliot, 1978 (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 7)
    - Tung, C.Y., 1976-1978 (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 8)
    - TV Project, undated (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 9)
    - Twentieth Century Fund, 1973 (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 10)
    - U: Miscellaneous [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 11)
    - United Nations, 1964, undated (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 12-13)
      Folder 13 is empty.
    - United States Chiefs Meeting: 1970 Sept. 27, 1969 (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 14-15)
    - United States Constitution, 1986 (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 16)
    - UPI, 1975 (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 17)
    - Usage Study, 1975 (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 18)
    - Vacations, 1973-1975, 1986 (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 19-22)
    - Vancouver, 1962-1971, undated (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 23)
    - Vancouver [RESTRICTED], 1962 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Vannevar Bush Fellowship: McElheny, 1984 (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 24)
    - Vartoogian, Linda, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 25)
    - Vartoogian, Linda [RESTRICTED], 1978-1983 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Vartoogian, Linda: Correspondence: Dick Duncan, 1978-1981 (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 26)
    - Vatican, 1962 (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 27)
    - Venezuela, undated (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 28)
    - Vice President: Agnew Follow Up, 1973 (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 29-30)
    - Videla: Sept. 7 or 8, 1977 (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 31)
    - Viet Nam: Coup, 1963, 1969 (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 32-34)
    - Vietnamese, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 35)
    - Visa: Copies, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 36)
    - Visa: Copies [RESTRICTED], 1972-1975 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Vivas, Felix E., 1974 (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 37)
    - Volcker, Paul: Lunch, 1979 (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 38)
    - Von Dohnanyi, Klaus [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 39)
    - Von Harling, H.B., undated (Offsite-box 3180, Folder 40)
    - Wage/Price Freeze, 1971 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 1)
    - Wanamaker, Melissa, 1978 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 2)
    - Wanamaker, Melissa [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R45)
    - War Casualties, 1975 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 3)
    - Warsaw, 1981 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 4)
    - Washington, 1963-1985 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 5-10)
    - Washington [RESTRICTED], 1975-1978 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Washington: Interns, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 11)
    - Washington: Memoranda, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 12)
    - Washington: Office Facilities, 1963-1972 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 13)
    - Washington: Political Meeting, 1959 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 14)
    - Washington Star, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 15)
    - Washington Star: Murray Gart, 1980 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 16)
    - Watergate, 1973 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 17)
    - West Africa, 1960-1965 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 18)
    - Westedit, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 19)
    - Western Union, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 20)
    - Whereabouts List Study, 1972 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 21)
    - White, Arthur, 1958-1985 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 22-23)
    - White, Arthur [RESTRICTED], 1979-1985 (Offsite-box R45)
    - White House Correspondents Dinner, 1977, 1986 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 24-25)
    - White House Fellows, undated (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 26)
    - Whitson, William, 1979 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 27)
    - Wierzynski, Gregory, 1969-1986 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 28-29)
    - Wierzynski, Gregory, 1975 (Offsite-box 3264, Folder 10)
    - Wierzynski, Gregory [RESTRICTED], 1983-1986 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Wilde, Jim: Monrovia, 1970-1981 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 30)
    - Wilde, Jim: Monrovia [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Wilhelm. John, 1959-1974 (Offsite-box 3181, Folder 31-32)
    - Wilhelm, John [RESTRICTED], 1963-1971 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Willwerth, Jim, 1977 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 1)
    - Wilson, Charles: Lunch, 1980 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 2)
    - Wire Services, 1973 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 3)
    - Witke, Roxane, 1974-1978 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 4)
    - Witke, Roxanne [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Woldegiorgis, Dawit: Lunch, 1986 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 5)
    - Wolf, Diether, 1981 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 6)
    - Women's Dummy, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 7)
    - Women's Magazine [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 8)
    - Wong Bing Wong: Trip: 1971, 1971-1985 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 9)
    - Wood, David, 1971-1980 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 10)
    - Wood, David [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Wood, David: Trip with Hedley Donovan, 1976 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 11)
    - Woodcock, Leonard: Lunch, 1973 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 12)
    - World Advertising Congress: Chicago, 1986 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 13)
    - World Memoranda, 1963-1975 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 14-15)
    - World Suggestions, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 16-19)
    - World War II Series, 1975 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 20-21)
    - Writing to Space, 1977 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 22)
    - Wurmstedt, Bob, 1973-1985 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 23-25)
    - Wurmstedt, Bob [RESTRICTED], 1979-1984 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Wux Wire Service, 1958 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 26)
    - Wynn, Wilton, 1962-1985 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 27-28)
    - Wynn, Wilton [RESTRICTED], 1967, 1977-1985 (Offsite-box R45)
    - X, Y, and Z: Miscellaneous [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 29)
    - Yang, John, 1981-1984 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 30)
    - Yang, John [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Yang, John Eric: Boston, 1979-1984 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 31)
    - Yang, John Eric: Boston [RESTRICTED], 1981-1986 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Yankelovich, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 3182, Folder 32-34)
    - Yankelovich, 1972-1985 (Offsite-box 3183, Folder 1-21)
      Folder 18 is empty.
    - Yankelovich [RESTRICTED], 1973, 1983 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Yankelovich: Survey Statistics, undated (Offsite-box 3183, Folder 22-23)
    - Yankelovich: Survey Statistics, undated (Offsite-box 3184, Folder 1)
    - Yankelovich: Values and Politics on Campus Study Results, 1971 (Offsite-box 3184, Folder 2-4)
    - Young, Andrew, 1977 (Offsite-box 3184, Folder 5)
    - Zamyatin, Leonid, 1970 (Offsite-box 3184, Folder 6)
  - Subseries I.E. Bureau Files, 1935-1984; 9.4 Linear feet in 11 record cartons
    The Bureau Files subseries contains materials from 1935 to 1984 and were collected by a variety of chiefs of correspondents. The materials within the series focus on the operations of various bureaus. While it is clear from the folder contents that chief of correspondents created the materials found in these folders, it is unclear who organized the materials which were separate from the other chief of correspondent files and featured their own style of organization. Contained within this series are clippings, dispatches, resumes, press releases, state department reports, expense reports, lists of bureau employees, floor plans, receipts, budgets, maps, overseas assignment directories, financial reports, stringer payment reports, biographical data sheets, requisition forms, job applications, legal documents, invoices, contracts, leases, and correspondence. The correspondence included in this series discusses staff issues, bureau operations, contacts, stringers, assignments, hiring, raises, salaries, expenses, reactions and criticisms of articles, travel plans, finances, payroll, money advances, leases, reimbursements, housing, and censorship.
    - Atlanta, 1957-1961, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 3188, Folder 3-4)
    - Atlanta [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Bad Godesberg, 1954-1957 (Offsite-box 3188, Folder 5-6)
    - Bad Godesberg [RESTRICTED], 1955 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Bad Godesberg: Life, 1954-1956 (Offsite-box 3188, Folder 7-9)
    - Bad Godesberg: Personnel, 1954-1957 (Offsite-box 3188, Folder 10-11)
    - Bad Godesberg: Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1955-1956 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Bad Godesberg: Photographer Stringers, 1957 (Offsite-box 3188, Folder 12)
    - Bad Godesberg: Time, 1955-1957 (Offsite-box 3188, Folder 13-15)
    - Bahrain, 1978-1984 (Offsite-box 3188, Folder 16-17)
    - Bahrain [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Baires: Legal Matters, 1958-1963 (Offsite-box 3188, Folder 18-19)
    - Baires: Legal Matters [RESTRICTED], 1960 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Baires: Personnel, 1963-1967 (Offsite-box 3188, Folder 20-21)
    - Bangkok, 1949-1951, 1961-1973 (Offsite-box 3188, Folder 22-28)
    - Bangkok, 1969, 1980-1985 (Offsite-box 3189, Folder 1-3)
    - Bangkok [RESTRICTED], 1981-1983 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Beijing, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 3189, Folder 4-5)
    - Beijing [RESTRICTED], 1980-1981 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Beirut, 1950-1961, 1969-1979 (Offsite-box 3189, Folder 6-12)
    - Beirut [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Bonn, 1945-1949, 1959-1962 (Offsite-box 3189, Folder 13-18)
    - Bonn, 1963-1983 (Offsite-box 3190, Folder 1-3)
    - Bonn: Personnel, 1952-1962 (Offsite-box 3190, Folder 4-10)
    - Bonn: Sports Illustrated, 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 3190, Folder 11)
    - Bonn: Time and Life, 1952-1957 (Offsite-box 3190, Folder 12-13)
    - Boston, 1957-1961, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 3190, Folder 14-16)
    - Boston [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Buenos Aires, 1943-1956 (Offsite-box 3190, Folder 17-20)
    - Buenos Aires [RESTRICTED], 1963, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Buenos Aires, 1954-1970, 1979-1985 (Offsite-box 3191, Folder 1-6)
    - Buenos Aires: Personnel, 1959-1962 (Offsite-box 3191, Folder 7)
    - Buenos Aires: Shea, Frank: Arrest, 1951 (Offsite-box 3191, Folder 8)
    - Cairo, 1946-1949, 1974-1983 (Offsite-box 3191, Folder 9-14)
    - Cairo [RESTRICTED], 1979-1983 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Calgary, 1956-1961 (Offsite-box 3191, Folder 15)
    - Caracas, 1963-1970 (Offsite-box 3191, Folder 16-17)
    - Caribbean, 1979-1983, undated (Offsite-box 3191, Folder 18-20)
    - Caribbean [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Central America: General: Stringers, 1955-1957 (Offsite-box 3191, Folder 21)
    - Chicago, 1956-1969, 1976-1983 (Offsite-box 3191, Folder 22-23)
    - Chicago, 1965-1968, 1974-1982 (Offsite-box 3192, Folder 1)
    - Continental Correspondents, 1935-1946 (Offsite-box 3192, Folder 2)
    - Detroit, 1976-1983 (Offsite-box 3192, Folder 3)
    - Eastern Europe, 1977-1983 (Offsite-box 3192, Folder 4-5)
    - Eastern Europe [RESTRICTED], 1978-1982 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Europe, 1975-1983 (Offsite-box 3192, Folder 6-7)
    - Frankfurt, 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 3192, Folder 8-9)
    - Germany: German Life Issues, 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 3192, Folder 10-11)
    - Hong Kong, 1972-1986 (Offsite-box 3192, Folder 12-14)
    - Hong Kong [RESTRICTED], 1979-1983 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Houston, 1978-1983 (Offsite-box 3192, Folder 15)
    - Jerusalem, 1970-1985 (Offsite-box 3192, Folder 16-20)
    - Jerusalem [RESTRICTED], 1976-1980 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Johannesburg, 1977-1986 (Offsite-box 3192, Folder 21)
    - Johannesburg, 1977-1980 (Offsite-box 3193, Folder 1-2)